[
    {
        "question": "Complete the title of this Gabriel García Márquez book “One Hundred Years of?",
        "answers": [
            "Solitude",
            "Discourage",
            "Revenge",
            "Love"
        ],
        "correct": "Solitude"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who wrote 'To Kill a Mockingbird'?",
        "answers": [
            "Marcel Proust",
            "Harper Lee",
            "James Joyce",
            "Virginia Woolf"
        ],
        "correct": "Harper Lee"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the second Harry Potter book?",
        "answers": [
            "Order of the Phoenix",
            "Prisoner of Azkaban",
            "Harry Potter and the Chamber of Secrets",
            "Half-Blood Prince"
        ],
        "correct": "Harry Potter and the Chamber of Secrets"
    },
    {
        "question": "Daniel Radcliffe became a global star because the film based on which book?",
        "answers": [
            "Ted",
            "Spy Kids",
            "Harry Potter",
            "Pirates of the Caribbean "
        ],
        "correct": "Harry Potter"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which book by Cheryl Strayed was adapted as a movie in 2014 by Reese Witherspoon?",
        "answers": [
            "Brave Enough",
            "Torch",
            "Wild",
            "Tiny beautiful things"
        ],
        "correct": "Wild"
    },
    {
        "question": "In which fantasy world is 'The Lion, the Witch, and the Wardrobe' by C.S. Lewis set?",
        "answers": [
            "Hogsmeade",
            "Far Far Away",
            "Narnia",
            "Esgaroth"
        ],
        "correct": "Narnia"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which 3 countries (apart from the US) does Elizabeth Gilbert travel to in 'Eat, Pray, Love'?",
        "answers": [
            "Italy, Greek and Spain",
            "England, Germany and Indonesia",
            "Finland, England and France",
            "Italy, India and Indonesia"
        ],
        "correct": "Italy, India and Indonesia"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which country is Paulo Coelho from?",
        "answers": [
            "Brazil",
            "Portugal",
            "Cape Verde",
            "Spain"
        ],
        "correct": "Brazil"
    },
    {
        "question": "When was 'Around the World in Eighty Days'  by Jules Verne published?",
        "answers": [
            "1997",
            "1985",
            "1872",
            "1889"
        ],
        "correct": "1872"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which British author wrote 'Wuthering Heights'?",
        "answers": [
            "Emily Brontë",
            "Martin Amis",
            "Douglas Adams",
            "Francis Leslie Ashton"
        ],
        "correct": "Emily Brontë"
    }
]